<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="61">
    <author>Achimobil</author>
    <version>0.2.0.0</version>
    <title>
		<en>Production Info Hud</en>
		<de>Produktionen Info Hud</de>
		<it>Hud Informazioni sulle produzioni</it>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[The first version of the productions Info Hud, known from the LS 19.

Publication on other sides only by myself, linking only with original download link. NO alternative link!
Changing or re-uploading, whether in whole or in part, is not allowed!

Since the LS19 version was built on Global Company dialogues and methods, this version nor now comes without setting options.

The current version has the following, non-customizable properties:
- Display of the active productions with their remaining time
- A production is only displayed if ...
- - it has less than 2 month remaining
- - it has less than 50% fill level
- The display is sorted according to the remaining time, whichever runs empty or is empty first is shown at the top
- Full productions are sortet in top of allowed
- Only the first 5 of the sortet list are shown

Requests and suggestions for improvement as well as error messages are always welcome.
These can be best done on my Discord in the channel of the mod. https://discord.gg/Va7JNnEkcW

If you don't like it, just don't use it.

Changelog 0.1.1.0
- Changes needed for the Giants Patch 1.2 for changed production times.
It still showns the left ingame days, but now it shows what get empty in 2 month, which is dependent from your settings of days per month. 

Changelog 0.2.0.0
- Productions with full output storage are now shown
- The font is now colored for full storage(red) and for missing resourced (orange)
- The mod is now translatable, en and de already added
- With left shift + P  you can turn on and of the display (configurable)
]]>
</en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[Die erste Version des aus dem LS 19 bekannten Produktionen Info Hud.

Upload auf anderen Seiten nur durch mich selbst, Verlinkung nur mit Original Downloadlink. KEIN Ersatzlink!
Das verändern sowie erneutes hochladen ob ganz oder in teilen ist nicht gestattet! 

Da die LS19 Version auf Global Company Dialoge und Methoden gebaut war, kommt diese Version jetzt erstmal ohne Einstellungsmöglichkeiten.

Die aktuelle Version hat folgende, nicht anpassbare Eigenschaften:
- Anzeige der aktiven Produktionen mit deren Restlaufzeit
- Angezeigt wird eine Produktion nur, wenn...
- - sie weniger als 2 Monate Restlaufzeit hat
- - sie weniger als 50% Füllstand hat
- Die Anzeige ist sortiert nach Restlaufzeit, was zuerst leer läuft oder leer ist steht oben
- Produktionen die Voll sind stehen noch darüber.
- Angezeigt werden nur die ersten 5 aus der sortierten Liste

Wünsche und Verbesserungsvorschläge sowie Fehlermeldungen sind immer willkommen.
Diese können am besten auf meinem Discord im Kanal des jeweiligen Mods gemacht werden. https://discord.gg/Va7JNnEkcW

Wem es nicht gefällt, der soll es einfach nicht benutzen.

Changelog 0.1.1.0
- Anpassung auf Patch 1.2.0.0 von Giants auf die geänderten Produktionen. 
Die Anzeige ist weiterhin in Ingame Tagen. 
Es wird aber angezeigt was in den nächsten 2 Monaten leer läuft, abhängig von den eingestellten Tagen pro Monat ist das unterschiedlich.

Changelog 0.2.0.0
- Produktionen mit vollem Ausgangslager werde als erstes angezeigt
- Die Schrift ist nun Farblich für volle Lager (rot) und für leere Eingangslager (Orange)
- Der Mod ist jetzt übersetzbar, en und de ist bereits enthalten
- Mit links shift + P kann die Anzeige aus un ein geschaltet werden (Einstellbar)
]]>
</de>
<it>
            <![CDATA[La prima versione delle produzioni Info Hud, conosciuta da LS 19.

Pubblicazione su altri siti solo da me, linkando solo con link di download originale. NESSUN collegamento alternativo!
Non è consentito modificare o ricaricare, né in tutto né in parte!

Poiché la versione LS19 è stata costruita su dialoghi e metodi Global Company, questa versione ora viene fornita senza opzioni di impostazione.

La versione corrente ha le seguenti proprietà non personalizzabili:
- Visualizzazione delle produzioni attive con il loro tempo residuo
- Una produzione viene visualizzata solo se ...
- - ha una durata residua inferiore a 2 mesi
- - è inferiore al 50% del livello di riempimento
- Il display è ordinato in base al tempo rimanente, quello che è vuoto o è vuoto per primo viene mostrato in alto
- Le produzioni che sono piene sono ancora al di sopra di esso.
- Vengono visualizzati solo i primi 5 dell'elenco ordinato

Richieste e suggerimenti di miglioramento così come messaggi di errore sono sempre ben accetti.
Questi possono essere fatti meglio sul mio Discord nel canale della rispettiva mod. https://discord.gg/Va7JNnEkcW

Se non ti piace, non usarlo.

Registro delle modifiche 0.1.1.0
- Adeguamento alla patch 1.2.0.0 da Giants alle produzioni modificate.
Il display è ancora nei giorni di gioco.
Tuttavia, viene visualizzato ciò che sarà vuoto nei prossimi 2 mesi, a seconda dei giorni impostati al mese, questo è diverso.

Registro modifiche 0.2.0.0
- Le produzioni con un magazzino di partenza completo vengono visualizzate per prime
- Il carattere ora è colorato per i magazzini pieni (rosso) e per i magazzini in entrata vuoti (arancione)
- La mod è ora traducibile, en e de è già inclusa
- Con shift a sinistra + P il display può essere spento e acceso (regolabile)
]]>
</it>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>ModIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

	<extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="ProductionInfoHud.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="TOGGLE_GUI">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_p" />
        </actionBinding>  
        <!-- <actionBinding action="OPEN_GUI"> -->
            <!-- <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lshift KEY_p" /> -->
        <!-- </actionBinding>         -->
    </inputBinding>   
    <actions>
        <action name="TOGGLE_GUI" />
        <!-- <action name="OPEN_GUI" /> -->
    </actions>
	<l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />
</modDesc>