<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="61">
    <author>Achimobil</author>
    <version>0.1.0.0</version>
    <title>
		<en>Production Info Hud</en>
		<de>Produktionen Info Hud</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[The first version of the productions Info Hud, known from the LS 19.

Since the LS19 version was built on Global Company dialogues and methods, this first version now comes without setting options.

The first version has the following, non-customizable properties:
- Display of the active productions with their remaining time
- A production is only displayed if ...
- - it has less than 72 hours remaining
- - it has less than 50% fill level
- The display is sorted according to the remaining time, whichever runs empty or is empty first is shown at the top

Requests and suggestions for improvement as well as error messages are always welcome.
These can be sent to me on modhoster via comment or PN.

If you don't like it, just don't use it.

Publication only with original download link. NO alternative link!
Changing or re-uploading, whether in whole or in part, is not allowed!
]]>
</en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[Die erste Versinn des aus dem LS 19 bekannten Produktionen Info Hud.

Da die LS19 Version auf Global Company Dialoge und Methoden gebaut war, kommt diese erste Version jetzt ohne Einstellungsmöglichkeiten.

Die erste version hat folgende, nich anpassbare Eigenschaften:
- Anzeige der aktiven Produktionen mit deren Restlaufzeit
- Angezeigt wird eine Produktion nur, wenn...
- - sie weniger als 72 Stunden Restlaufzeit hat
- - sie weniger als 50% füllstand hat
- Die Anzeige ist sortiert nach Restlaufzeit, was zuerst leer läuft oder leer ist steht oben

Wünsche und Verbesserungsvorschläge sowie Fehlermeldungen sind immer willkommen.
Diese können mir auf modhoster per Kommentar or PN geschickt werden.

Wem es nicht gefällt, der soll es einfach nicht benutzen.

Veröffentlichung nur mit Original Downloadlink. KEIN Ersatzlink!
Das verändern sowie erneutes hochladen ob ganz oder in teilen ist nicht gestattet!
]]>
</de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>ModIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

	<extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="ProductionInfoHud.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>